Bang!
Bye!
OK. Good morning.
Good morning.
What's the temperature?
It's 6 degrees 4.
Good morning.
Good morning, Rogue.
Good morning. You use a good camera.
It's 6 degrees 3.
It is 6 degrees 3.
I forgot to eat the yogurt at home.
Eat it tomorrow.
I will eat it tomorrow.
I'll do my best.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
Long time no see pit.
I will do my best.
Today is Sendai pit.
Yay!
It's very early in the morning and I'm a little swollen.
It's hard work.
I didn't do anything.
Yuna is cute even when she's all sloppy.
Good morning.
She's so cute. What's this?
She's holding up her middle finger.
It's cute.
Can I say that? Grand.
No, you can't.
It's a grand, so yes.
It's cute.
The Identification Squad will identify it for you.
He's holding up his middle finger.
That's great.
Amazing.
It's so colorful.
Cute.
Buy the mask stripe.
For example.
3,000 yen.
I'll give it away.
I dyed it. I dyed all the heads.
We are dyed friends, right?
I'm a senior bleach artist.
For many years, really.
I won't bleach my hair for maybe another year.
But I want to get fancy hair.
I want all of my hair to be reborn soon.
I think it's really great.
How hard it is to bleach.
I've already bleached my hair 10+ times.
Yay.
When it takes 2 years.
It is in the refrigerator.
With water.
It's a bit realistic here.
Don't look at it.
Energy drinks everywhere.
Good morning.
I misunderstood the meeting time.
I'm late.
Now.
The guy at the store...
David didn't know.
We didn't know either.
We had no idea.
We had a hard time finding him.
What if you open it and it changes?
I'll open it.
Oh, my God.
What if it opens and changes?
Good morning.
We're making drinks.
What are you making?
A drink for your throat.
I'm making a drink for your throat.
Laughs.
It's going to be red, and it's going to fly higher.
Sky of Courage
Anaro anaro
Soar more
Such coolness
More in the world
Putting the future in
Now in your dreams
Snowman School
I've been hit. I'm going to bed early.
I'm speaking now. It's before rehearsal.
My hair is a mess.
I can't!
Okay, let's do it again. Three, two, one. Okay.
I'm pretty sure I got the face wrong.
Okay.Okay.
Oh, sound check. I've got to go next.
I'm pretty sure I got my face wrong.
I'm going.
I'm tired.
Staff voice.
I'm going. Are you okay?
Please.
Please, I'm begging you.
Staff's voice
Voice of Staff
Good morning.
I look forward to working with you.
You're very good. That's right.
Rehearsal is over.
Ah, Mike.
Rehearsal over.
End.
This is the current part.
It's over. Rehearsal. I will do my best.
It's over.
Let's eat dinner.
I'm anxious. I'm so anxious.
I'm anxious.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to die.
I want to put a slit in, after all.
Please do.
Let's go!
I'll do my best!
Please do it.
I'll do my best.
I'm trying.
But there's a white one.
You're wearing it? You're wearing it? Is it on?
There.
The blue one from Hedman's.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go around here.
Okay.
Hikaru!
Hanane!
Maasa!
Miyu!
British staff culture!
Let's go!
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best. I'm looking forward to it!
Today is the center epeat.
In this picture, I'm wearing
I'm wearing a costume.
This is Hitami.
I want to see it.
I'm going.
Moku moku. Let's go!
Oh!
connect
ran
me
Ahhhhhh...
I've decided, but I'll forget about it because it's not fun to be depressed here.
Sorry everyone. There are days like this.
This is real.
It's coming.
Well, I'll take it!
Tournament's over.
It's over.
Part of it is over.
It was fun.
I'll do my best for the second part.
Wait.
It's over.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
It was a lot of fun.
It was great.
I love Tohoku-san.
It was wonderful. Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la.
I thought the costumes were nice.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
I thought the costumes were good.
I have to think I'm going to get it out.
P.P.
Yes, I thought it was a good idea.
Above.
But I'm partially calm.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's starting.
Karen Hina'sKaren Hina's
Ryu Hikaru
Kanya Wada Yuna
Rine Ignite Soccer Bleacher
New timing.
Good timing.
Can do.
Motivation 100% vigor.
Motivation: 100% energy
Motivation 100%.
I had a big nose.
I thought I was going to die.
I'm fine.
Good work.
It's good.
Good.
Oh, you idiot.
I'm not stupid.
Fish face
Deep-sea fish feelings
Stupid.
Are you used to feeling like a deep-sea fish?
Thank you for your hard work.
It's Pero, who can't understand.
Our favorite point.
This is our favorite point.
I love it.
Ro...
Cute.
And the tits.
I've never done anything like this.
I've been doing it.
You do it every second.
It's fast.
It's getting faster.
That's cute.
He's cute.
I've been thinking how much I want to meet him.
I've been saying it for a long time.
Even during rehearsal, I was thinking how much I wanted to meet you.
It's so cute, isn't it?
You're still commuting to work.
I wonder.
Please don't look at it too much and buy it today.
Yes, you can.
No, you can't. The teacher.
I heard teachers don't sell them.
That's normal.
It's just for today.
That's right.
You can't even try to take a picture.
Thanks for your hard work.
Good morning.
It's done!
We did it!
Thank you for your hard work.
Binaryity gone, but could you say it?
It's cool.
It's gone.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Thanks for your hard work.
See you next time in Toyosu.
Thank you. I love you all.
Thank you.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It was fun.
My voice is rattling.
I'm Shibuko, who did her best.
Yay.
Thank you very much.